<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ATM Shop</string>
    <string name="tomorrow">Tomorrow</string>
    <string name="today">Today</string>
    <string name="yesterday">Yesterday</string>
    <string name="Rs">\u20B9</string>


    <!--drawer-->
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="openDrawer">open_drawer</string>
    <string name="closeDrawer">close_drawer</string>

    <!-- Navigation Drawer menu labels -->
    <string name="nav_home">Add Shop Detail</string>
    <string name="nav_shop_dtls">Your Shops</string>
    <string name="nav_share">Share App</string>


    <!-- Toolbar titles when navigation menu item is selected -->
    <string-array name="nav_item_activity_titles">
        <item>Add Shop Detail</item>
        <item>Your Shops</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="activity_title_about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="activity_title_privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="action_clear_all">Clear All</string>
    <string name="action_logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="action_mark_all_read">Mark All as Read</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="str_about_us">ABOUT APP\n\n
ATM SHOP is combination of some essential requirement to rent out your shop for ATM available in a SINGLE platform to make things simple.\n
1. Owner details\n
2. Shop Location details\n
3. shop dimension details\n
4. Shop Rent details\n
5. Shop Photos\n
6. Questionaries’\n
You can share to your family or friends or colleagues.\n\n
Please call 9890799930 for more information and features.\n
About Company:-\n
We are a new-age ATM consulting Company. Our Services is available in Pan India. We provide highly professional and transparent services in the field of real estate. You will appreciate that as we are settled in PUNE have gained sufficient experience in ATM consultancy, we can give you reliable and trouble free services for renting of property for ATM
\nPlease call 9890799930 for more information and features.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="str_terms">
(1)	Slab shop\n\n
(2)	Space of the shop should be 10 X 10 X 10\n\n
(3)	A separate power meter of single phase 3 kv with main cable upto ATM room .\n\n
(4)	3 X 10 space to put hoarding of title “ ATM “\n\n
(5)	Space to install  “LOLLYPOP “\n\n
(6)	Space to put “ TOTEM POLE “ and AC outdoor units\n\n
(7)	A space of 6 X 6 on the terrace or on the shop to install V-Sat ( Dish ) ( If its not a plain surface there the expenses to be borne by the owner to make it flat )\n\n
(8)	A rent free “ Fit out  period “ of 60 days .\n\n
(9)	An advance rent of one month after signing the LOI and of two months’ rent after signing the agreement with the ATM company will be giving by a cheque.\n\n
(10)	Rent agreement will be of maximum 9 years\n\n
(11)	Three months rent and service tax needs to be paid as a consulting fee.\n\n
(12)	Consulting fees to be paid immediately after LOI sign.\n\n
(13)	No objection letter to install V-Sat dish ,Photo copy of pan card ,One cancel cheque ,Photo copy of Bank pass book of the shop owner and light bill of the shop should be submitted.\n\n
(14)	Photo copy of the documents of the shop required for the agreement.\n\n
(15)	The shop shown for the ATM can not be changed in any condition , failure to which a penality will be charged to the owner.\n\n
Office Contact No.:  9890799930\n\n

एटीएम मशीन के लिए नियम और शर्तें\n

(1)   स्लैब की दुकान.\n
(2)   दुकान की जगह 10 X 10 X 10 होनी चाहिए.\n
(3)   एटीएम कमरे तक मुख्य केबल के साथ single phase 3 kv  का एक अलग बिजली मीटर.\n
(4)   शीर्षक "एटीएम" की जमाखोरी रखने के लिए  3 X 10 स्थान.\n
(5)   "LOLLYPOP" स्थापित करने के लिए स्थान.\n
(6)    "TOTEM POLE" और एसी आउटडोर इकाइयां डाल करने के लिए स्थान.\n
(7)   छत पर 6 X 6 की स्थान V-Sat (डिश) को स्थापित करने के लिए दुकान पर (यदि इसकी कोई सादा सतह नहीं है तो मालिक द्वारा उसे सपाट बनाने के लिए खर्च मालिक द्वारा  भुगतान किया जाना है.\n
(8)    60 दिनों के लिए "निःशुल्क अवधि" का किराया मुक्त।\n
(9)    अग्रिम किराया चेक द्वारा  LOI पर हस्ताक्षर करने के बाद एक महीने का किराए और एटीएम कंपनी के साथ समझौते पर हस्ताक्षर करने के बाद दो महीने का किराए दिया जाएगा।\n
(10)   किराया अनुबंध अधिकतम 9 वर्षों का होगा.\n
(11)   कंसल्टिंग फीस के रूप में तीन महीने का किराया और सेवा कर देना होगा।\n
(12)   LOI  पर हस्ताक्षर करने के तुरंत बाद कंसल्टिंग शुल्क का भुगतान करना होगा.\n
(13)   अनुमोदन के बाद   वी-सैट डिश स्थापित करने के लिए नोबजेक्शन पत्र, पैन कार्ड की फोटो प्रति, एक रद्द चेक , दुकान के मालिक की बैंक पास बुक की फोटो कॉपी और दुकान के लाइट बिल को जमा करें।\n
(14)    समझौते के लिए आवश्यक दुकान के दस्तावेजों की फोटो प्रति।\n
(15)   एटीएम के लिए दिखाया गया दुकान किसी भी हालत में बदला नहीं जा सकता है, या फिर मालिक को दंड लगाया जाएगा।\n\n
कार्यालय संपर्क नंबर: 9890799930\n
</string>
</resources>
